export const secondRound = {
  topic: "Irregular Verbs",
  level: "Intermediate",
  totalQuestions: 10,
  perQuestionScore: 3,
  questions: [
    {
      question:
        "It ___ a long time since I watched an episode of One-Punch Man.",
      choices: ["was", "is", "has been", "were"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "has been",
    },
    {
      question:
        'Where __ you __ this hoodie? It looks cool!',
      choices: ['did/bought', 'has/bought', 'did/buy', 'do/buys'],
      type: 'MCQs',
      correctAnswer: 'did/buy',
    },
    {
      question: "I __ too much coffee today.",
      choices: ["have had", "has had", "had had", "was having"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "have had",
    },
    {
      question: "I wish I __ more about this topic before I got started.",
      choices: ["have heared", "heard", "had heard", "hore"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "had heard",
    },
    {
      question: "I will __ to them tomorrow.",
      choices: ["speaks", "spoke", "have spoken", "speak"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "speak",
    },
    {
      question: "__ you ever __ your keys only to find them in the most stupid place one week later?",
      choices: ["do/lose", "did/lost", "have/lost", "are/losing"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "have/lost",
    },
    {
      question: "We're so behind our work, I __ you we should have started sooner.",
      choices: ["told", "have told", "telled", "am told"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "told",
    },
    {
      question: "I __ already __ the house when you called me.",
      choices: ["am/leaving", "had/left", "have/left", "was/leaving"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "had/left",
    },
    {
      question: "__ you __ your friend to school yesterday?",
      choices: ["did/bringed", "have/bring", "have/brought", "did/bring"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "did/bring",
    },
    {
      question: "I __ never __ so many Schokobons in my life!",
      choices: ["have/ate", "was/eating", "have/eaten", "am/eaten"],
      type: "MCQs",
      correctAnswer: "have/eaten",
    },
  ],
};
